http://www.blackstone-ney.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
You are hereHome About UsPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
We value the importance of your personal privacy as it applies to your visit to our web site.  This site uses Insite Metrics and Google Analytics which are both metrics software that collect data about site visitors.What We CollectWhat website you came from to get here.How long you stay for.What kind of computer you’re using.Anonymous and personal data, depending on what you do during your visit adn on what personal information you elect to give us.What We ShareWe do not sell, lease or otherwise share any personal information about our visitors with or to any third party companies or individuals.We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on this company; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of our company or (c) act to protect the personal safety of the employees of our company and other users of the web site.What We Use"Cookies"We use cookies to store information about your activities on our web site. We use this information to anonymously track your visit to our site. Even if you elect to give us personal information, that information will never appear in the cookies. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. You can disable cookies (consult support information from your browser's publisher). If you disable cookies, your visit to our site will not be significantly effected though, from time to time, we may provide special features that require the use of cookies. JavaScriptWe use JavaScript to enhance our web site and to assist in the tracking of anonymous data. If you disable JavaScript, many of the features on our web site will not work. Web Beacons (Clear Gifs)We may use "Web Beacons" together with cookies to track your activities on our web site through Insite Metrics. Generally, Web Beacons allow third party agents (tracking technology providers) to track web site activity on behalf of their customers. Our "Web Beacons" are designed to provide no tracking information in cases where a visitor's cookies are disabled. Our use of Web Beacons conforms to or exceeds the Network Advertising Initiative's Web Beacon Guidelines. Web Server Log FilesWe use web server log files to gather summary information about activities on our web site. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring documents, and operating system. We analyze this information to extract trends such as popular search engines and search terms and popular referrers . We also use this information to maintain the successful operation of our web servers. We do not use web server log files to track either anonymous or identifiable users. What do we do with your data? The tracking information allows us to better understand the kind of people who come to our site and what content they’re reading. This allows us to make better decisions about design and writing.All of our activity related to Google Analytics use falls within the bounds of the Google Analytics Terms of Service.Want to opt out of tracking?You can opt out of Google’s advertising tracking cookie or use a browser plugin to opt out of all Google Analytics tracking software. Layout Request FormFirst NameLast NameWork ContactCompany NameIndustry --Alternate EnergyArmament & AmmunitionAutomotiveAviation & AerospaceEducationElectronicsGeneral Mfg.Heavy Duty TruckMedia & SemiconductorMedicalOff-RoadOpticsOther TransportationPharmaceuticalPlating & Surface FinishingSemiconductorSolarDefenseOil & GasRe-manufacturingIntegratorOtherEmail addressPhoneState or ProvinceCountryProductMessage Submit
Access to our download files requires a one-time registration.
First Name
Last Name
Work Contact
Company Name
Industry
--Alternate EnergyArmament & AmmunitionAutomotiveAviation & AerospaceEducationElectronicsGeneral Mfg.Heavy Duty TruckMedia & SemiconductorMedicalOff-RoadOpticsOther TransportationPharmaceuticalPlating & Surface FinishingSemiconductorSolarDefenseOil & GasRe-manufacturingIntegratorOther
Email address
Phone
State or Province
Country
Submit
Access to our download files requires a one-time registration.First NameLast NameCompany Name
Industry
--Alternate EnergyArmament & AmmunitionAutomotiveAviation & AerospaceEducationElectronicsGeneral Mfg.Heavy Duty TruckMedia & SemiconductorMedicalOff-RoadOpticsOther TransportationPharmaceuticalPlating & Surface FinishingSemiconductorSolarDefenseOil & GasRe-manufacturingIntegratorOtherWork ContactEmail addressPhoneState or ProvinceCountry Submit
Name * Email address * Company * Work Contact
Industry
--Alternate EnergyArmament & AmmunitionAutomotiveAviation & AerospaceEducationElectronicsGeneral Mfg.Heavy Duty TruckMedia & SemiconductorMedicalOff-RoadOpticsOther TransportationPharmaceuticalPlating & Surface FinishingSemiconductorSolarDefenseOil & GasRe-manufacturingIntegratorOther
Address * City * State * Zip * Country * Phone * Product Part Description * Please fill out as much of the following information as possible to help us configure the right product for your needs.Max Part Size/Weight Min Part Size/Weight Part Material Temp Limits Contamination Production Rate Parts in a Basket Yes
No Submit* denotes a required field
Need help choosing the right cleaning equipment for your facility?Contact UsEducation & News
